Finding Aid for the Music Department Photograph Collection, circa 1920-2008
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Photographs, circa 1920-2008, I.
  - Harriet Simons, conductor with University at Buffalo Choir receiving applause, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-047)
  - Slee Hall, inside concert hall, November 22 1981, 1 black and white photograph; Nowak, Edward L. (Box 7, Item MD07-048)
  - Slee Hall, inside concert hall, November 22 1981, 1 black and white photograph; Nowak, Edward L. (Box 7, Item MD07-049)
  - Slee Hall, inside concert hall, November 22 1981, 1 black and white photograph; Nowak, Edward L. (Box 7, Item MD07-050)
  - Slee Hall, exterior, July 15 1985, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-051)
  - Slee Hall, exterior, July 15 1985, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-052)
  - Slee Hall organ, October 17 1988, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-053)
  - Slee Hall organ, Op. 95, C.B. Fisk pipe shop, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-054)
  - Slee Hall organ, Op. 95, C.B. Fisk pipe shop, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-055)
  - Slee Hall organ, Op. 95, C.B. Fisk pipe shop, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-056)
  - Slee Hall organ, Op. 95, C.B. Fisk pipe shop, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-057)
  - Slee Hall organ, Op. 95, C.B. Fisk pipe shop, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-058)
  - Slee Hall organ, Op. 95, C.B. Fisk pipe shop, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-059)
  - Slee Hall organ, Op. 95, C.B. Fisk pipe shop, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-060)
  - Slee Hall organ, Op. 95, C.B. Fisk pipe shop, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-061)
  - Slee Hall organ, Op. 95, C.B. Fisk pipe shop, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-062)
  - Slee Hall organ, Op. 95, C.B. Fisk pipe shop, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-063)
  - Slee Hall organ, Op. 95, C.B. Fisk pipe shop, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-064)
  - Slee Hall organ, Op. 95, C.B. Fisk pipe shop, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-065)
  - Slee Hall organ, Op. 95, C.B. Fisk pipe shop, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-066)
  - Slee Hall organ, Op. 95, C.B. Fisk pipe shop, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-067)
  - Slee Hall organ, Op. 95, C.B. Fisk pipe shop, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-068)
  - Slee Hall organ, Op. 95, C.B. Fisk pipe shop, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-069)
  - Slee Hall organ, Op. 95, C.B. Fisk pipe shop, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-070)
  - Slee Hall organ, Op. 95, C.B. Fisk pipe shop, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-071)
  - Slee Hall organ, Op. 95, C.B. Fisk pipe shop, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-072)
  - Slee Hall organ, Op. 95, C.B. Fisk pipe shop, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-073)
  - Slee Hall organ, Op. 95, C.B. Fisk pipe shop, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-074)
  - Slee Hall organ, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-075)
  - Slee Hall organ, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-076)
  - Slee Hall organ, Op. 95, C.B. Fisk pipe shop, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-077)
  - Dallas model organ, by C.B. Fisk, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-078)
  - Dallas model organ, by C.B. Fisk, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-079)
  - Slee Hall organ, Op. 95, C.B. Fisk pipe shop, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-080)
  - Slee Hall organ, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-081)
  - Slee Hall organ, Op. 95, C.B. Fisk pipe shop, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-082)
  - Slee Hall organ, Op. 95, C.B. Fisk pipe shop, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-083)
  - Slee Hall organ, Op. 95, C.B. Fisk pipe shop, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-084)
  - Slee Hall organ, Op. 95, C.B. Fisk pipe shop, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-085)
  - Slee Hall organ, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-086)
  - Slee Hall organ, Op. 95, C.B. Fisk pipe shop, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-087)
  - Slee Hall organ, Op. 95, C.B. Fisk pipe shop, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-088)
  - Slee Hall organ, Op. 95, C.B. Fisk pipe shop, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-089)
  - Slee Hall organ, Op. 95, C.B. Fisk pipe shop, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-090)
  - Slee Hall organ, Op. 95, C.B. Fisk pipe shop, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-091)
  - Leo Smit, composer, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-092)
  - Leo Smit, composer on stage with Creative Associates, February 1972, 1 black and white photograph; Greenberg-May Prod. (Buffalo) (Box 7, Item MD07-093)
  - Leo Smit, composer conducting student ensemble, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-094)
  - Leo Smit, composer playing piano, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-095)
  - Leo Smit, composer at piano with jazz pianist Pete Johnson, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-096)
  - Mark Sokol, violinist rehearsing with Creative Associates, November 1970, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 8, Item MD08-001)
  - Mark Sokol, violinist rehearsing with Creative Associates, November 1970, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 8, Item MD08-002)
  - Delmar A. Stewart, violist, September 23 1973, 1 black and white photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 8, Item MD08-003)
  - Andrew Stiller, composer playing bassoon, 1971-1972, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 8, Item MD08-004)
  - Edmond Strainchamps, faculty member teaching music theory, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 8, Item MD08-005)
  - Edmond Strainchamps, faculty member teaching music theory, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 8, Item MD08-006)
  - Morton Subotnick, composer holding score in one hand, cigarette in the other, 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 8, Item MD08-007)
  - Morton Subotnick, composer holding score in one hand, cigarette in the other, 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 8, Item MD08-008)
  - Morton Subotnick, composer conducting with Yuji Takahashi in foreground at piano, December 15 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 8, Item MD08-009)
  - Henrik Svitzer, flutist on piccolo, 1976-1977, 1 black and white photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 8, Item MD08-010)
  - Henryk Szeryng, violinist giving a masterclass on stage, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 8, Item MD08-011)
  - Aki Takahashi, pianist (contact sheet), undated, 1 black and white contact sheet; Unidentified (Box 8, Item MD08-012)
  - Yuji Takahashi, composer at piano, 1967-1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 8, Item MD08-013)
  - Toru Takemitsu, composer, December 1977, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 8, Item MD08-014)
  - Toru Takemitsu, composer, December 1977, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 8, Item MD08-015)
  - Toru Takemitsu, composer, December 1977, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 8, Item MD08-016)
  - Toru Takemitsu, composer, December 1977, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 8, Item MD08-017)
  - Augusta Read Thomas, composer, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Montanus, James (Box 8, Item MD08-018)
  - Suzanne Thomas, harpist performing with University at Buffalo Wind Ensemble, December 2 1978, 1 black and white photograph; Smith, Robert L (Box 8, Item MD08-019)
  - William Thomson, faculty member laying last few bricks of Baird Hall (North Campus), November 9 1979, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 8, Item MD08-020)
  - John Tilbury, pianist standing outdoors, Fall 1977, 1 black and white photograph; Seman, David (Box 8, Item MD08-021)
  - Judy Treible, with Ed Emshwiller, and Woody B. Vasulka, August 1974, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 8, Item MD08-022)
  - David Tudor, composer at console with Renée Levine in background, at rehearsal of his work, Rainforest May 12 1974, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 8, Item MD08-023)
  - David Tudor, composer at console, at rehearsal of his work, Rainforest May 12 1974, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 8, Item MD08-024)
  - David Tudor, composer, at rehearsal of his work, Rainforest May 12 1974, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 8, Item MD08-025)
  - University at Buffalo Percussion Ensemble in performance, March 3 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 8, Item MD08-026)
  - University at Buffalo Percussion Ensemble in performance, March 3 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 8, Item MD08-027)
  - Vermeer Quartet, sitting outdoors, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 8, Item MD08-028)
  - Marijke Verberne, violoncellist performing with Tom Coleman, November 3 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 8, Item MD08-029)
  - Klaus von Wrochem, composer standing with harp, 1966-1967, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 8, Item MD08-030)
  - Klaus von Wrochem, composer, his Stücke (1966), March 19 1967, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 8, Item MD08-031)
  - Klaus von Wrochem, composer, his Stücke (1966), March 19 1967, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 8, Item MD08-032)
  - Klaus von Wrochem, composer, his Stücke (1966), March 19 1967, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 8, Item MD08-033)
  - Klaus von Wrochem, composer, his Stücke (1966), March 19 1967, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 8, Item MD08-034)
  - Klaus von Wrochem, composer, his Stücke (1966), March 19 1967, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 8, Item MD08-035)
  - Klaus von Wrochem, composer, his Stücke (1966), March 19 1967, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 8, Item MD08-036)
  - Gwendolin Sims Warren, vocalist, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 8, Item MD08-037)
  - Gwendolin Sims Warren, vocalist standing outdoors with Evelyne Crochet, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 8, Item MD08-038)
  - Gwendolin Warren Sims, vocalist performing with Barbara Conrad and Laurence Bogue, November 3 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 8, Item MD08-039)
  - Gwendolin Warren Sims, vocalist performing with Barbara Conrad and Laurence Bogue, November 3 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 8, Item MD08-040)
  - Howard Weiss, violinist, November 16 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 8, Item MD08-041)
  - Andrew Nathaniel White, oboist balancing on top of a trunk, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 8, Item MD08-042)
  - Andrew Nathaniel White, oboist, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 8, Item MD08-043)
  - Andrew Nathaniel White, oboist, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 8, Item MD08-044)
  - Jan Williams, percussionist walking with John Bergamo, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Sinderbrand (Box 8, Item MD08-045)
  - Jan Williams, percussionist standing at steps of Albright-Knox Art Gallery, 1974-1975, 1 black and white photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 8, Item MD08-046)
  - Jan Williams, percussionist, 1966, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 8, Item MD08-047)
  - Jan Williams, percussionist, April 29 1967, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 8, Item MD08-048)
  - Jan Williams, percussionist performing with Edward Burnham, November 5 1967, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 8, Item MD08-049)
  - Jan Williams, percussionist striking a gong, 1967-1968, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 8, Item MD08-050)
  - Jan Williams, percussionist conducting Creative Associates, December 12 1971, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 8, Item MD08-051)
  - Jan Williams, percussionist with Creative Associates, December 12 1971, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 8, Item MD08-052)
  - Jan Williams, percussionist, right arm raised, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 8, Item MD08-053)
  - Jan Williams, percussionist conducting rehearsal (contact sheet), undated, 1 black and white contact sheet; Unidentified (Box 8, Item MD08-054)
  - Jan Williams, percussionist rehearsing with Creative Associates, November 1 1975, 1 black and white photograph; Rusiniak, Chris (Box 8, Item MD08-055)
  - Jan Williams, percussionist conducting Creative Associates, March 19 1978, 1 black and white photograph; Haupt, Irene (Box 8, Item MD08-056)
  - Jan Williams, percussionist rehearsing with Creative Associates, February 12 1978, 1 black and white photograph; Haupt, Irene (Box 8, Item MD08-057)
  - Jan Williams, percussionist with Creative Associates, 1974-1975, 1 black and white photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 8, Item MD08-058)
  - Jan Williams, percussionist conducting (contact sheet), undated, 1 black and white contact sheet; Unidentified (Box 8, Item MD08-059)
  - Jan Williams, percussionist conducting Creative Associates in performance (contact sheet), 1977-1978, 1 black and white contact sheet; Unidentified (Box 8, Item MD08-060)
  - Jan Williams, percussionist conducting, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 8, Item MD08-061)
  - Jan Williams, percussionist seated with Renée Levine outside Albright-Knox Art Gallery, 1974-1975, 1 black and white photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 8, Item MD08-062)
  - Jan Williams, percussionist seated with Renée Levine outside Albright-Knox Art Gallery, 1974-1975, 1 black and white photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 8, Item MD08-063)
  - Jan Williams, percussionist seated outside Albright-Knox Art Gallery, 1974-1975, 1 black and white photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 8, Item MD08-064)
  - Muriel Herbert Wolf, vocalist working with a student, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 8, Item MD08-065)
  - Muriel Herbert Wolf, vocalist working with a student, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 8, Item MD08-066)
  - Charles Wuorinen, composer conducting, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Rudolph, Klaus (Box 8, Item MD08-067)
  - Robert Donington, musicologist seated with bass viola da gamba and unidentified woman at harpsichord, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Ter Maat, Rich (Box 9, Item MD09-001)
  - Boris Kroyt, violist coaching student string quartet, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fudold (Box 9, Item MD09-002)
  - Boris Kroyt, violist coaching student string quartet, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fudold (Box 9, Item MD09-003)
  - Boris Kroyt, violist coaching student string quartet, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fudold (Box 9, Item MD09-004)
  - Boris Kroyt, violist coaching student string quartet, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fudold (Box 9, Item MD09-005)
  - Boris Kroyt, violist coaching student string quartet, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fudold (Box 9, Item MD09-006)
  - Boris Kroyt, violist coaching student string quartet, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fudold (Box 9, Item MD09-007)
  - Alexander Schneider, violinist coaching student double bassists, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fudold (Box 9, Item MD09-008)
  - Alexander Schneider, violinist coaching student double bassists, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fudold (Box 9, Item MD09-009)
  - Alexander Schneider, violinist coaching student double bassists, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fudold (Box 9, Item MD09-010)
  - Alexander Schneider, violinist coaching student double bassists, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fudold (Box 9, Item MD09-011)
  - Alexander Schneider, violinist, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fudold (Box 9, Item MD09-012)
  - Alexander Schneider, violinist conducting while holding violin, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fudold (Box 9, Item MD09-013)
  - Alexander Schneider, violinist playing violin, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fudold (Box 9, Item MD09-014)
  - Alexander Schneider, violinist pointing bow, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fudold (Box 9, Item MD09-015)
  - Alexander Schneider, violinist conducting while holding violin, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fudold (Box 9, Item MD09-016)
  - Alexander Schneider, violinist conducting while holding violin, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fudold (Box 9, Item MD09-017)
  - Mischa Schneider, violoncellist working with students, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fudold (Box 9, Item MD09-018)
  - Mischa Schneider, violoncellist working with students, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fudold (Box 9, Item MD09-019)
  - Mischa Schneider, violoncellist working with students, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fudold (Box 9, Item MD09-020)
  - Mischa Schneider, violoncellist working with students, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fudold (Box 9, Item MD09-021)
  - Mischa Schneider, violoncellist working with students, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fudold (Box 9, Item MD09-022)
  - Mischa Schneider, violoncellist working with students, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fudold (Box 9, Item MD09-023)
  - Trumpet players, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 9, Item MD09-024)
  - Brass players, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 9, Item MD09-025)
  - Young girl accompanying violinist, undated, 1 black and white photograph; George, M. (Buffalo) (Box 9, Item MD09-026)
  - Buffalo Academy of Music (1852-1955), 1868, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 9, Item MD09-027)
  - Joe Ford, saxophonist with double bassist Sabu Adeyola, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Marinaccio, Lou (Box 9, Item MD09-028)
  - Michael Tilson Thomas, conductor, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 9, Item MD09-029)
  - Creative Associates peering into Renée Levine's office through window -- Renée Levine is standing behind her desk, facing camera, September 23, 1973, 1 black and white photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 9, Item MD09-030)
Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the Library's online catalog.
Contributors
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Dept.
Subjects
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Dept. --Photographs; C. B. Fisk (Firm); Composers--Photographs; Musicians--Photographs; Music--New York (State)--Buffalo--Photographs; Organ (Musical instrument)--New York (State)--Buffalo--Photographs
Genres
Photographs; Black-and-white photographs; Portraits